Guide to the New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council Records WAG.123
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Hotel Files, circa 1930-1986
  - Crown Motel, 1964-1977 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Croyden, 1951-1975 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Dauphin, Undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Delmonico, 1931-1981 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Delmonico: Dues, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Devon, 1951-1961 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Diplomat, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Dixie, 1939-1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Dixie: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Doral Inn: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Doral Park Avenue, 1966-1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Doral Park Avenue: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Dorset, Undated; 1956-1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Dorset: Dues, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Drake, 1939-1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Drake: Dues, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Drake: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Drake: Leaflets, Undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Dunfey, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Earle, Undated; 1953-1973 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Earle: Dues, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - East End, 1952-1974 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Edison, 1937-1976 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Elysee: Organzing, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Embassy: Leaflets, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Emerson, Undated; 1940 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Emerson: Dues, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Emigrant Industrial Savings Bank: Organizing, 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Empire: Dues, 1940-1944 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Esplanade, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Esplanade: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Essex House, 1939-1943 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Essex House: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Essex House: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Executive, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Fifth Avenue, Undated; 1938-1977 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Fifth Avenue: Dues, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Fifth Avenue: Leaflets, Undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Forest Hills: Leaflets, Undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Forrest, Undated, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Forrest: Dues, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Forty-Fourth Street: Organizing, Undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Four Seasons, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Fourteen: Organizing, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Franconia, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Franconia: Dues, 1942-1943 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Franklin Arms, 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Franklin Towers, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - George Washington, 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - George Washington: Dues, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - George Washington: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - George Washington: Leaflets, Undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Gotham, 1939-1943 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Gotham: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Gotham: Leaflets, Undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Governor Clinton, 1939-1953 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Governor Clinton: Leaflets, 1930s-1950s (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Governor Clinton: Strike, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Gramercy Park, 1941-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Gramercy Park: Dues, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Gramercy Park: Leaflets, Undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Granada, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Granada: Dues, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Grand Hyatt, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Grand Hyatt: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Grand Hyatt New York: Layoffs, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Grand Union: Dues, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Great Northern, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Gregorian, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Greystone, 1941-1943 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Greystone: Dues, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Greystone: Leaflets, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Grosvenor, Undated; 1958-1965 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Half Moon, 1940-1943 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Halloran House, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Halloran House: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Hampshire House, 1939-1943 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Hilton, 1950-1960 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Hilton, 1963-1968 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Hilton: Leaflets, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Holiday Inn: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Holley: Dues, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Holley and Holley Chambers, 1942-1943 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Howard Johnson's: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Hyde Park, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Intercontinental, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Intercontinental: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - International, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Iroquois, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Kimberly, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - King Edward, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - King Edward: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Kings Crown: Leaflets, Undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Knickerbocker, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Knickerbocker: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Knott: Leaflets, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - La Guardia Airport, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Langdon: Leaflets, Undated (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - La Salle, 1940-1943 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - La Salle: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Lexington, 1939-1945 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Lincoln, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Lincoln: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Lombardy, 1939-1943 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Lombardy: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Lowell, Undated; 1983 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Madison, 1939-1965 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Madison: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Madison Square: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Madison Square: Leaflets, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Mansfield, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Marcy, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Marcy: Dues, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Mariette-Woodside, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Marriott: Pickets, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Marriott-La Guardia, Undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Martha Washington, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Martinique, 1939-1943 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Mayflower, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Mayflower: Dues, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Mayflower: Dues, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Mayflower: Leaflets, Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - McAlpin, 1939-1967 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - McAlpin, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - McAlpin: Dues, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - McAlpin: Dues, Jan-Jun 1944 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - McAlpin: Dues, Jul-Dec 1944 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - McAlpin: Leaflets, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Meridien: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Meurice, Undated; 1941 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Milford Plaza, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Milford Plaza: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Milner, Undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Murray Hill, 1939-1943 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Murray Hill: Dues, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Navarro, 1939-1941 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - New Weston, 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - New Weston: Dues, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - New Yorker, 1937-1972 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - New Yorker: Bankruptcy, 1963-1965 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - New Yorker: Bankruptcy, 1966-1971 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - New Yorker: Dues, Mar-May 1943 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - New Yorker: Dues, Aug 1943 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - New Yorker: Dues, Sep 1943 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - New Yorker: Dues, Jan-Apr 1944 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - New Yorker: Dues, Jun 1944 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - New Yorker: Dues, Sep 1944 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - New Yorker: Leaflets, 1938-1955 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - New Yorker: Separation and Termination Plant Survey, A-B, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - New Yorker: Separation and Termination Plant Survey, C-F, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - New Yorker: Separation and Termination Plant Survey, G-K, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - New Yorker: Separation and Termination Plant Survey, L-N, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - New Yorker: Separation and Termination Plant Survey, O-R, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - New Yorker: Separation and Termination Plant Survey, S-Z, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - New York Hilton: Layoffs, 1982-1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - New York Penta, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - New York Penta: Layoffs, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - New York Sheraton, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - New York Sheraton: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - New York Statler: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Olcott, Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Oliver Cromwell, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Oliver Cromwell: Dues, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Oliver Cromwell: Dues, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Oliver Cromwell: Dues, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Omni Park Central, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - One Fifth Avenue, Undated; 1937-1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - One Fifth Avenue: Dues, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - One Tenth Avenue: Dues, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Palace, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Palace: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Paramount, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Paramount: Leaflets, Undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Paris, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Paris: Dues, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Paris: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Park Avenue, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Park Central, 1937-1943 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Park Central: Leaflets, Undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Park Crescent, Undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Park Crescent: Dues, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Park Lane, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Park Lane: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Park Lane: Leaflets, Undated (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Park Plaza, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Park Plaza: Dues, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Park Royal, Undated (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Park Royal: Leaflets, Undated (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Parkside, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Parkside: Dues, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Parkside::Leaflets, Undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Park View, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Penn: Dues, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Penn Valet: Dues, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Pennsylvania, 1939-1943 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Pennsylvania: Dues, Apr-Jun 1943 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Pennsylvania: Dues, Jul-Sep 1943 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Pennsylvania: Dues, Oct-Dec 1943 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Pennsylvania: Leaflets, 1940s (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Peter Cooper, Undated (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Piccadilly, Undated (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Piccadilly: Dues, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Piccadilly Coffee Shop, 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Piccadilly Restaurant: Severance Pay, 1976-1985 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Pickwick Arms, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Pierre, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Pierre: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Pierre: Leaflets, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Pierrepont, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Pierrepont: Layoffs, Undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Plaza, 1939-1965 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Plaza, 1966-1977 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Plaza: Dues, Jan-Mar 1943 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Plaza: Dues, May-Dec 1943 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Plaza: Dues, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Plaza: Layoff, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Plymouth, Undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Plymouth: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Portman, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - President, Undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - President: Dues, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Prince George, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Prince George: Dues, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Prince George: Leaflets, Undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Raleigh, 1939-1943 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Raleigh: Dues, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Raleigh: Leaflets, Undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Regency, Undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Regent, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Ritz-Carlton, Undated; 1950-1951 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Ritz-Carlton: Leaflets, Undated (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Ritz Towers, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Ritz Towers: Dues, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Ritz Towers: Dues, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Ritz Towers: Leaflets, Undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Ritz Towers: Organizing, 1939-1943 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Riverside Plaza, Undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Robert Fulton, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Robert Fulton: Leaflets, Undated (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Roosevelt, 1938-1943 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Roosevelt: Dues, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Roosevelt: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Roosevelt: Leaflets, Undated (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Royal Manhattan, 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Royal Manhattan: Separation, Vacation, and Termination Surveys, A-B, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Royal Manhattan: Separation, Vacation, and Termination Surveys, C-D, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Royal Manhattan: Separation, Vacation, and Termination Surveys, E-H, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Royal Manhattan: Separation, Vacation, and Termination Surveys, J-L, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Royal Manhattan: Separation, Vacation, and Termination Surveys, S-V, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Russell, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Russell: Dues, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Russel: Leaflets, Undated (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - St. George, 1937-1942 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - St. George, 1946-1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - St. George: Dues, Jan-Jun 1942 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - St. George: Dues, Aug-Dec 1942 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - St. George: Dues, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - St. George: Leaflets, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - St. Moritz, 1939-1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - St. Moritz: Dues, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - St. Moritz: Dues, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - St. Moritz: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - St. Moritz: Leaflets, Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - St. Regis, 1939-1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - St. Regis: Dues, May-Jul 1939 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - St. Regis: Dues, Aug-Dec 1939 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - St. Regis: Dues, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - St. Regis: Dues, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - St. Regis: Dues, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - St. Regis: Leaflets, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - St. Regis-Sheraton, Undated; 1977 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - St. Regis-Sheraton: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Salisbury, 1959-1962 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Salisbury: Dues, 1942-1944 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Sanford, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Sanford: Leaflets, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Savoy Hilton, 1959-1964 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Savoy Plaza, Undated; 1939-1965 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Savoy Plaza: Dues, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Savoy Plaza: Dues, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Savoy Plaza: Leaflets, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Seventy Park Ave., 1958 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Seville, 1951-1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Seymour, 1954-1964 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Shelburne-East Gate, 1962, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Shelton, 1953-1965 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Shelton: Dues, 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Shelton: Dues, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Shelton: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Shelton: Leaflets, Undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Sheraton: Dues, 1941-1944 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Sheraton: Leaflets, 1955-1962 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Sheraton: Savings Plan, Undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Sheraton Centre New York: Layoffs, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Sheraton East, 1965-1974 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Sheraton La Guardia, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Sheraton Motor Inn, 1962-1974 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Sheraton Tenney, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Sherry-Netherland, 1939-1965 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Sherry-Netherland, 1966-1975 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Sherry-Netherland: Dues, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Sherry-Netherland: Layoffs, Undated; 1943 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Skyline, 1975-1978 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Skyline: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Stadium, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Stanhope, 1951-1962 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Statler, Undated; 1953 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Statler-Hilton, 1951-1962 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Strafford: Dues, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Sulgrave, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Sulgrave: Dues, 1940-1944 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Summit, Undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Sutton, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Sutton: Dues, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Taft, 1946-1969 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Taft, 1970-1984 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Taft: Dues, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Taft: Dues, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Taft: Dues, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Taft: Dues, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Ten Park Ave., 1951-1976 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Theresa, 1941-1965 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Theresa: Dues, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Theresa: Dues, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Theresa: Dues, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Times Square, 1953-1977 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Times Square: Dues, 1939-1942 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Towers, 1952-1973 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Towers: Leaflets, Undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Townhouse, 1951-1974 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Townhouse 44, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Travelodge: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Tudor, 1943-1976 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Tudor: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Tudor: Leaflets, Undated (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Tuscany, 1952-1976 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Tuscany: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Tuscany: Leaflets, Undated (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - United Nations Plaza, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - United Nations Plaza: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - University Hotel, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Van Cortland, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Vanderbilt, Undated; 1952-1963 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Vanderbilt: Dues, 1939-1940 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Vanderbilt: Dues, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Vanderbilt: Leaflets, Undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Van Rensselaer, 1940-1942 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Victoria, 1939-1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Victoria: Dues, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Victoria: Leaflets, Undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Viscount, Undated (Box 32, Folder 9A)
  - Vista, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Volney, 1957-1976 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Waldorf-Astoria, 1913, 1931-1936 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Waldorf-Astoria, 1937-1939 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Waldorf-Astoria, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Waldorf-Astoria, 1942-1946 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Waldorf-Astoria, 1947-1975 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Waldorf-Astoria: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Waldorf-Astoria: Layoffs, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Waldorf-Astoria: Leaflets, Undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Warrington, 1940-1967 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Warwick, Undated; 1941-1943, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Warwick: Leaflets, Undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Webster, 1939, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Wellington, Undated; 1953-1975 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Wellington: Dues, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Wellington: Leaflets, Undated (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Wentworth, 1959-1977 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Wentworth: Dues, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Wentworth: Dues, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Westbury, 1942-1978 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Westbury: Leaflets, Undated (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - West End Manor, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Westner, 1943-1963 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - White: Dues, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Whitehall, 1939-1976 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Whitehall: Dues, 1940-1942 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Wilson, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Windermere, 1952-1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Windsor, 1969-1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Winslow, 1952-1969 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Winslow: Dues, 1939-1940 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Winslow: Dues, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Winslow: Dues, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Winthrop, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Winthrop: Dues, 1939-1940 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Winthrop: Dues, 1954-1975 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Wolcott, 1954-1975 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Wolcott: Dues, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Woodstock, 1939-1974 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Woodstock: Dues, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Woodstock: Dues, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Woodstock: Dues, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Woodward, 1952-1959 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Woodward: Dues, 1939-1941 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Wyndham, 1949-1977 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Wyndham: Dues, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Wyndham: Dues, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Series V: Neighborhood Service Councils, 1961-1976
  Series V: Neighborhood Service Councils, 1961-1976, brings together files on the many programs and services provided by the HTC's social service councils; these include legal services, housing services, health care provision, cultural programs, sports, camps for children and others. The files also document the Service Councils's relations with other public and private agencies such as the Boy Scouts, Legal Aid, the YM- and YWCA, etc.
  - General, 1961-1972 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Adult Activities Program, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Adult Program, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Adult Program aUndated Classes, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Annual Trophy Awards, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Poverty, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Ballet Concert, 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Baseball, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Baseball, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Baseball, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Baseball: Junior Team, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Baseball: Records, 1963-1968 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Baseball: Schedules, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Board of Education, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1963-1965 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Bronx Mailings, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn, Undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Brooklyn: Table Tennis, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - California Trip, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Camera Club, 1966-1968 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Camp Programs, 1965-1968 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Camps: Anti-Poverty Program, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Central Labor Council: Classes, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Christmas Party, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Christmas Party, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Christmas Party, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Christmas Party, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Civil Rights, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Consumer: A-C, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Consumer: D-H, 1969, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Consumer: J-M, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Consumer: N-S, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Consumer: T-W, 1973-1975 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Consumer Assembly, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Consumer Fraud Letters, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Consumer Issues, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Consumer Problems, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Consumers, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Consumers, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Consumers, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence: A-B, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence: C, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence: D-F, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence: G-J, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence: H, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence: I-L, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: M, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Correspondencee: N-O, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: P-Q, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: R, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: S, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Correspondencee: T-W, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Legislators, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Programs, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Programs, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Dance, 1964-1967 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Dance, 1968-1970 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Dance, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Day Care Camps, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Delegation to Albany, Mar 1965 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Delegation to Albany, May 1965 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Election Campaign: Mailings to CaUndatedidates aUndated Members, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Elections, 1966, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Elections: Legislative, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Expo, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Family Medical, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Fishing Club, Undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Garnishes, 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Grenadiers BaUndated, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Hotel Delegates, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Housing, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Housing, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Housing: A-B, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Housing: C-F, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 29)